Siavash Ebrahimi Darsinouei

Dubai - UAE | +971 55 236 4938 | ebrahimi.siavash@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I am a software engineer with strong web and game development skills. I am interested in designing immersive and interactive Web apps, Native apps, VR experiences and video games. I have advanced problem-solving and leadership skills, and am fluent in English and Farsi. Please visit my website and my GitHub account to view my portfolio.

Education

CareerFoundry Dubai, UAE

Full-Stack Web Development Program Expected: July 2023

Yazd Azad University
B.S. Environmental Studies

May 2004

Certificates

SAE Institute Dubai

Game Development Nov 2021

FORTINET NSE Institute Online, Dubai

NSE 1 Network Security Associate

NSE 2 Network Security Associate

August 22, 2020

September 10, 2020

University of Michigan Online, Dubai

Introduction to Data Science in Python

Applied Plotting, Charting & Data Representation in Python

Jun 08, 2020

July 12, 2020

Business Idea Center (BIC) of Tehran
Business Development and Communication.

Jun 2014

Canadian University of DubaiDubai, UAEEnglish for Business CommunicationJuly 2009

Work Experience

Freelance Web and Unity Developer

Dubai, UAE

October 2021 - Present

• Designed and developed Web apps (PWA), Native apps (Mobile), 3D games, and VR environments using multiple technologies and tools including HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, jQuery, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js, React-Native, Angular, Unity, C#, Maya, Adobe Photoshop & Premiere.

Blue Marine Shipping

Dubai, UAE

Business Development Manager

July 2018 - Present

- Developed and maintained the long-term relationships with the clients, business partners and prospects in the EMEA region.
- Studied the target markets and provided market insights to the sales and marketing teams, supporting their decision-making process.

Account Manager

July 2013 – July 2018

• Maintained the relationship with the clients, identified and managed sales lead and upsell opportunities according to the annual sales KPIs.

Siavash Ebrahimi Darsinouei

Dubai - UAE | +971 55 236 4938 | ebrahimi.siavash@gmail.com

Sabz Energy Tejarat Arvand LLC Commercial Advisor

Tehran, Iran & Remote

March 2016 - July 2018

 Provided market analytical insights to support the management team amend and approve the business strategy plans.

Fn Touch Dubai, UAE

Co-Founder & Commercial Manager

June 2008 – May 2013

• Developed the pricing strategy and managed the financial transactions related to the distribution of a wide range of IoT products.

Aryavand Tehran Co.

Tehran, Iran

Sales and Service Director (Printers Division)

June 2004 – May 2008

- Supervised the distribution of large format printers to advertisement firms throughout the country.
- Conducted national training courses regarding the operation and maintenance of large-format printers.

Languages and Interests

- Languages: English (Fluent), Farsi (Native)
- Interests: Travelling, Music, Movies, Reading, Space.